<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<artist>
  <name>Piero Piccioni</name>
  <albums>
    <album>100 Years of Pasolini: The Early Days</album>
    <album>50 Lounge Bar Grooves, Vol. 3 (The Best International Chillout for Your Relaxing Cafè)</album>
    <album>70's Soundtracks</album>
    <album>A Modern Gentleman - The Refined And Bittersweet Sound Of An Italian Maestro</album>
    <album>Alberto Sordi - Le Colonne Sonore</album>
    <album>Amore mio aiutami - Help Me My Love (Original Motion Picture Soundtrack)</album>
    <album>Amore mio aiutami (Dream Version)</album>
    <album>Amore mio aiutami (Original Motion Picture Soundtrack)</album>
    <album>Anna Karenina (Original Motion Picture Soundtrack)</album>
    <album>Beat, Vol. 2</album>
    <album>Bello, onesto, emigrato Australia sposerebbe compaesana illibata (Original Motion Picture Soundtrack)</album>
    <album>Best of Piero Piccioni</album>
    <album>Boom! Italian Jazz Soundtracks At Their Finest (1959-1969)</album>
    <album>Bora Bora</album>
    <album>Bora Bora (Deluxe) (Colonna sonora del film)</album>
    <album>Cadaveri eccellenti - Falcone (Original Motion Picture Soundtracks)</album>
    <album>Camille 2000 (Original Motion Picture Soundtrack)</album>
    <album>Camille 2000 (Tape Remasters)</album>
    <album>Chi dice donna dice donna (Original Motion Picture Soundtrack)</album>
    <album>Colette: Piero Piccioni</album>
    <album>Colpo Rovente - Red Hot Shot (Original Motion Picture Soundtrack)</album>
    <album>Dopo di che uccide il maschio e lo divora - Marta (Original Motion Picture Soundtrack)</album>
    <album>Eternal Melodies: The Best of Romance Soundtracks</album>
    <album>Greatest Movie Themes, Vol. 2</album>
    <album>Homage: Piero Piccioni Symphonic Soundtracks (Live in Rome) (2021 Remaster)</album>
    <album>I giovani tigri - The Young Tigers (Original Motion Picture Soundtrack)</album>
    <album>Il Dio sotto la pelle - God Under the Skin (Original Motion Picture Soundtrack)</album>
    <album>Il giustiziere di Dio (Original Motion Picture Soundtrack)</album>
    <album>Il medico della mutua (Original Motion Picture Soundtrack)</album>
    <album>Incontri Proibiti - Forbidden Encounters (Original Motion Picture Soundtrack)</album>
    <album>Italian Dinner Lounge Music</album>
    <album>Kidnap - Fatevi vivi la polizia non interverrà (Original Motion Picture Soundtrack)</album>
    <album>L'Italia vista dal cielo (Original Motion Picture Soundtrack)</album>
    <album>La Colonna Sonora Italiana: Piero Piccioni - Vol. 1</album>
    <album>La musica di Piero Piccioni Vol. 2</album>
    <album>La notte brava (Original Motion Picture Soundtrack)</album>
    <album>Love themes in music: An Italian Love Story</album>
    <album>Lucky Luciano</album>
    <album>Monte Carlo Cocktail Lounge Party: Classic Bossa Nova Sounds, Vol. 2</album>
    <album>Peccato Mortale (Colonna sonora originale)</album>
    <album>Piero Piccioni - Classics Christmas Collection</album>
    <album>Piero Piccioni & Orchestra 014 (Live at Forum Studios, Rome) (Anniversary Edition)</album>
    <album>Piero Piccioni & Orchestra 014 (Live at Ravenna Festival)</album>
    <album>Piero Piccioni 60-80's (Remastered)</album>
    <album>Piero Piccioni in Liebesthemen</album>
    <album>Piero Piccioni Love Themes</album>
    <album>Piero Piccioni Music - Christmas Collection</album>
    <album>Piero Piccioni Romance - Best Love Songs in Movies</album>
    <album>Piero Piccioni Romantic Music</album>
    <album>Piero Piccioni Soundtracks</album>
    <album>Piero Piccioni Soundtracks Vol. 2</album>
    <album>Piero Piccioni Soundtracks Vol. 3</album>
    <album>Piero Piccioni Unreleased</album>
    <album>Piero Piccioni, Love Scores</album>
    <album>Romantic Strings</album>
    <album>Romantic Strings, Vol. 2</album>
    <album>Smoke Over London (Original Motion Picture Soundtrack) (Deluxe Edition)</album>
    <album>Spaghetti Western Soundtracks - Vol. 5</album>
    <album>The Best of Piero Piccioni Vol. 2</album>
    <album>The Best of Piero Piccioni Vol. 3</album>
    <album>The Italian Soundtrack Vol. 2 - Piero Piccioni (Original Film Scores)</album>
    <album>The Italian Summer - Dreamy Old Money Music</album>
    <album>The Sounds of Rome</album>
    <album>Ti Ho Sposato Per Allegria (Original Motion Picture Soundtrack)</album>
    <album>Traffic Boom (From "Tutto a posto e niente in ordine" and "The Big Lebowski")</album>
    <album>Tutto a posto e niente in ordine (Original Motion Picture Soundtrack) (Deluxe Edition)</album>
    <album>Un Italiano in America (Original Motion Picture Soundtrack)</album>
    <album>Una Vita Violenta - Violent Life (Original Motion Picture Soundtrack)</album>
    <album>Una vita violenta (Original Motion Picture Soundtrack)</album>
  </albums>
</artist>