<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<artist>
  <name>AVID Professional Karaoke</name>
  <albums>
    <album>70s Karaoke Classics (Professional Backing Track Version)</album>
    <album>All Time Greatest Disco Karaoke (Professional Backing Track Version)</album>
    <album>Best Ever Karaoke (Professional Backing Track Version)</album>
    <album>Christmas Karaoke (Professional Backing Track Version)</album>
    <album>Greatest Millennium Karaoke Party (Professional Backing Track Version)</album>
    <album>Karaoke Classics (Professional Backing Track Version)</album>
    <album>Karaoke Duets (Professional Backing Track Version)</album>
    <album>Karaoke Motown (Professional Backing Track Version)</album>
    <album>Karaoke Pop Hits (Professional Backing Track Version)</album>
    <album>Karaoke Rock In The USA (Professional Backing Track Version)</album>
    <album>Phil Collins Karaoke (Professional Backing Track Version)</album>
    <album>Super Karaoke Hits (Professional Backing Track Version)</album>
    <album>Super Karaoke Hits 2006 (Professional Backing Track Version)</album>
    <album>Super Karaoke Hits 2010 (Professional Backing Track Version)</album>
    <album>Super Karaoke Hits 2016 (Professional Backing Track Version)</album>
    <album>Super Karaoke Hits 2017 (Professional Backing Track Version)</album>
    <album>The Greatest Karaoke…Ever! Vol 2 (Professional Backing Track Version)</album>
    <album>The Spy Who Karaoked Me! (Professional Backing Track Version)</album>
    <album>The Ultimate Karaoke Chart Album (Professional Backing Track Version)</album>
    <album>The Very Best Karaoke Duets with Don't Go Breaking My Heart, I Got You Babe, You're the One That I Want, And All Your Favorite Mal</album>
    <album>Ultimate Christmas Karaoke (Professional Backing Track Version)</album>
    <album>Ultimate Karaoke Classics (Professional Backing Track Version)</album>
    <album>Ultimate Karaoke Duets (Professional Backing Track Version)</album>
    <album>Wow! Karaoke To Your Favourite Dance Hits (Professional Backing Track Version)</album>
    <album>Wow! Karaoke To Your Favourite Dance Hits Vol 3 (Professional Backing Track Version)</album>
  </albums>
</artist>