<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<artist>
  <name>Allan Sherman</name>
  <albums>
    <album>'50s & '60s Lost & Found Records Vol. 3</album>
    <album>Allan Sherman is My Son the Nut</album>
    <album>Allan Sherman is Nutty But Nice (Not Naughty But Nice) [Live]</album>
    <album>Allan Sherman Is the Cat in the Hat and Other Dr Seuss Stories – Bonus Edition</album>
    <album>Allan Sherman Nutty but Nice</album>
    <album>Allan Sherman sings Number Ones (and others, too)</album>
    <album>Camp Granada</album>
    <album>Camp Granada (Hello Muddah Hello Faddah, I Am Back at Camp Grenada)</album>
    <album>Camp Granada (Hello Mudder Hello Fadder, Here I Am At Camp Grenada)</album>
    <album>Camp Granada (Hello Mudder, Hello Fadder, Here I Am At Camp Grenada) (feat. Allen "Mother Father" Sherman) - Single</album>
    <album>Camp Grenada (Hello Muddah Hello Faddah, I Am Back At Camp Granada)</album>
    <album>Cat in the Hat and More Songs Like That</album>
    <album>Funny Camp Songs</album>
    <album>Funny Camp Songs from Camp Granada</album>
    <album>Funny Campfire Songs from Camp Granada</album>
    <album>Funny Letters from Camp</album>
    <album>Hello Mater, Hello Pater (British Version of Hello Muddah, Hello Fadduh) (feat. Allen "Camp Granada" Sherman) - Single</album>
    <album>Hello Mother Hello Father, Here I am at Camp Granada</album>
    <album>Hello Mother, Hello Father</album>
    <album>Hello Muddah Hello Faddah (A Funny Letter from Camp)</album>
    <album>Hello Muddah Hello Faddah, I Am Back At Camp Granada</album>
    <album>Hello Muddah, Hello Fadduh</album>
    <album>Hello Muddah, Hello Fadduh! (A Letter from Camp Granada) Live Version (feat. Allen "Mudduh Faddah Camp Grenada" Sherman) - Single</album>
    <album>Hello Mudder</album>
    <album>Live at the Hollywood Bowl</album>
    <album>Live At The Sands</album>
    <album>My Son the Nut</album>
    <album>My Son The Nut</album>
    <album>My Son the Nut in Concert</album>
    <album>Number One Hits (And Others Too)</album>
    <album>Number One Hits (And Others, Too) Best of Allan Sherman’s Greatest Hits</album>
    <album>Pink Noise, Brown Noise, Gray Noise, Green Noise, and Hours of Soothing Sounds for BetterSleep for Babies</album>
    <album>Return to Camp Granada (Hello Muddah, Hello Fadduh, I Am Back At Camp Grenada) [feat. Allen "Mudduh Faddah" Sherman]</album>
    <album>The Drinking Man's Diet (feat. Allen Muddah Faddah Camp Granada Sherman)</album>
    <album>xxxxx</album>
  </albums>
</artist>