<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<artist>
  <name>John Powell</name>
  <albums>
    <album>Action! - Iconic Soundtracks</album>
    <album>At the Foot of Yonders Mountain</album>
    <album>BOLT</album>
    <album>Chicken Run</album>
    <album>Cinéma - Soundtrack Masters</album>
    <album>Don't Worry Darling (Score from the Original Motion Picture Soundtrack)</album>
    <album>Dr. Seuss' Horton Hears A Who! (Original Motion Picture Soundtrack)</album>
    <album>Dr. Seuss' The Lorax (Original Motion Picture Score)</album>
    <album>Evolution (Original Motion Picture Soundtrack)</album>
    <album>Fair Game (Original Motion Picture Score)</album>
    <album>Ferdinand (Original Motion Picture Score)</album>
    <album>Film Suites, Vol. 1</album>
    <album>Gigli (Original Motion Picture Score)</album>
    <album>Hancock (Original Motion Picture Soundtrack)</album>
    <album>Happy Feet (Original Score)</album>
    <album>Happy Feet Two (Music from The Motion Picture) (Deluxe Edition)</album>
    <album>How To Train Your Dragon (Deluxe Edition)</album>
    <album>How To Train Your Dragon (Music From The Motion Picture)</album>
    <album>How to Train Your Dragon (Original Motion Picture Soundtrack)</album>
    <album>How to Train Your Dragon 2 (Music from the Motion Picture)</album>
    <album>How to Train Your Dragon 2 (Music from the Motion Picture) (The Deluxe Edition)</album>
    <album>How To Train Your Dragon- The Hidden World (Original Motion Picture Soundtrack)</album>
    <album>How To Train Your Dragon- The Hidden World (The Deluxe Edition)</album>
    <album>How To Train Your Dragon: The Hidden World (Original Motion Picture Soundtrack)</album>
    <album>How To Train Your Dragon: The Hidden World (The Deluxe Edition)</album>
    <album>Hubris- Choral Works by John Powell</album>
    <album>I Am Sam (Original Motion Picture Score)</album>
    <album>Ice Age- Continental Drift (Original Motion Picture Score)</album>
    <album>Ice Age- Dawn Of The Dinosaurs</album>
    <album>Ice Age- The Meltdown (Original Motion Picture Soundtrack)</album>
    <album>Ice Age: Continental Drift (Original Motion Picture Score)</album>
    <album>Ice Age: Dawn Of The Dinosaurs</album>
    <album>Ice Age: The Meltdown (Original Motion Picture Soundtrack)</album>
    <album>Jason Bourne (Original Motion Picture Soundtrack)</album>
    <album>Jumper (Original Motion Picture Soundtrack)</album>
    <album>Just Visiting (Original Motion Picture Soundtrack)</album>
    <album>Knight And Day</album>
    <album>Kung Fu Panda 2 (Music From The Motion Picture)</album>
    <album>Mars Needs Moms</album>
    <album>Mars Needs Moms (Original Motion Picture Soundtrack)</album>
    <album>Migration (Original Motion Picture Soundtrack)</album>
    <album>Mr. & Mrs. Smith (Original Motion Picture Score)</album>
    <album>P.S. I Love You</album>
    <album>Pan (Original Motion Picture Soundtrack)</album>
    <album>Paycheck (Original Motion Picture Soundtrack - Deluxe Edition)</album>
    <album>Paycheck (Original Motion Picture Soundtrack)</album>
    <album>Piano Solos from -The Call of the Wild-</album>
    <album>Piano Solos from "The Call of the Wild"</album>
    <album>Piano Solos from How to Train Your Dragon- The Hidden World</album>
    <album>Rio (Original Motion Picture Score)</album>
    <album>Rio 2 (Original Motion Picture Soundtrack)</album>
    <album>Robots (Original Motion Picture Score)</album>
    <album>Solo: A Star Wars Story (Original Motion Picture Soundtrack)</album>
    <album>Still- A Michael J. Fox Movie (Soundtrack From The Apple Original Film)</album>
    <album>Still: A Michael J. Fox Movie (Soundtrack From The Apple Original Film)</album>
    <album>Stop-Loss (Music From The Motion Picture)</album>
    <album>Test Driving Toothless (from How to Train Your Dragon)</album>
    <album>That Christmas (Soundtrack from the Netflix Film)</album>
    <album>The Bourne Identity (Original Motion Picture Soundtrack - 20th Anniversary Tumescent Edition)</album>
    <album>The Bourne Identity (Original Motion Picture Soundtrack)</album>
    <album>The Bourne Supremacy (Original Motion Picture Soundtrack)</album>
    <album>The Bourne Ultimatum</album>
    <album>The Call of the Wild (Original Motion Picture Soundtrack)</album>
    <album>The Green Zone (Original Motion Picture Soundtrack)</album>
    <album>The Italian Job (Original Motion Picture Soundtrack)</album>
    <album>Thelma The Unicorn (Soundtrack from the Netflix Film)</album>
    <album>Two Weeks Notice (Original Motion Picture Score)</album>
    <album>United 93 (Original Motion Picture Soundtrack)</album>
    <album>Wicked: The Original Motion Picture Score</album>
    <album>X-Men- The Last Stand (Original Motion Picture Soundtrack)</album>
    <album>X-Men: The Last Stand (Original Motion Picture Soundtrack)</album>
  </albums>
</artist>