<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<artist>
  <name>James Horner</name>
  <albums>
    <album>-Batteries Not Included</album>
    <album>"A Cinematic Life: Iconic Soundtracks"</album>
    <album>A Beautiful Mind (Original Motion Picture Soundtrack)</album>
    <album>Action! - Iconic Soundtracks</album>
    <album>Aliens: The Deluxe Edition (Original Motion Picture Soundtrack)</album>
    <album>All The King's Men (Original Motion Picture Soundtrack)</album>
    <album>An American Tail</album>
    <album>An American Tail- Fievel Goes West</album>
    <album>An American Tail: Fievel Goes West</album>
    <album>Apocalypto</album>
    <album>Apocalypto (Score)</album>
    <album>Apollo 13 (Original Motion Picture Soundtrack)</album>
    <album>AVATAR Music From The Motion Picture Music Composed and Conducted by James Horner</album>
    <album>AVATAR Music From The Motion Picture Music Composed and Conducted by James Horner (Deluxe)</album>
    <album>AVATAR Music From The Motion Picture Music Composed and Conducted by James Horner [Deluxe]</album>
    <album>Back to Titanic - More Music from the Motion Picture</album>
    <album>Balto</album>
    <album>Battle Beyond the Stars</album>
    <album>Best Of Arnold Schwarzenegger Vol. 2</album>
    <album>Beyond Borders (Original Motion Picture Soundtrack)</album>
    <album>Bicentennial Man - Original Motion Picture Soundtrack</album>
    <album>Bicentennial Man (Original Motion Picture Soundtrack)</album>
    <album>Black Gold (Original Motion Picture Soundtrack)</album>
    <album>Bobby Jones- Stroke Of Genius (Original Motion Picture Soundtrack)</album>
    <album>Bopha! (Original Motion Picture Soundtrack)</album>
    <album>Brainstorm (Original Motion Picture Score)</album>
    <album>Braveheart (Original Motion Picture Soundtrack)</album>
    <album>Casper</album>
    <album>Cinéma - Soundtrack Masters</album>
    <album>Class Action (Original Motion Picture Soundtrack)</album>
    <album>Cocoon (Original Motion Picture Soundtrack)</album>
    <album>Dad</album>
    <album>Deadly Blessing (Music from the Original Motion Picture Soundtrack)</album>
    <album>Deep Impact - Music from the Motion Picture</album>
    <album>Dog Music - Relaxing Sounds for Dogs</album>
    <album>Dr. Seuss' How The Grinch Stole Christmas</album>
    <album>Dr. Seuss' How the Grinch Stole Christmas (Original Motion Picture Soundtrack) - Expanded Edition</album>
    <album>Enemy At The Gates - Original Motion Picture Soundtrack</album>
    <album>Flightplan</album>
    <album>For Greater Glory- The True Story Of Cristiada (Original Motion Picture Soundtrack)</album>
    <album>For Greater Glory: The True Story Of Cristiada (Original Motion Picture Soundtrack)</album>
    <album>Gorky Park (Original Motion Picture Soundtrack)</album>
    <album>Great Movie Love Themes</album>
    <album>Honey, I Shrunk the Kids (Original Motion Picture Soundtrack)</album>
    <album>House Of Sand And Fog (Original Motion Picture Soundtrack)</album>
    <album>Humanoids From The Deep</album>
    <album>Humanoids from the Deep (ISC495)</album>
    <album>I See You [Theme from Avatar] (Cosmic Gate Club Mix)</album>
    <album>IRIS - Original Motion Picture Soundtrack</album>
    <album>James Horner - Collage- The Last Work</album>
    <album>James Horner - The Classics</album>
    <album>JUMANJI  ORIGINAL MOTION PICTURE SOUNDTRACK</album>
    <album>JUMANJI ORIGINAL MOTION PICTURE SOUNDTRACK</album>
    <album>Legends Of The Fall Original Motion Picture Soundtrack</album>
    <album>Mighty Joe Young</album>
    <album>More Music from Braveheart</album>
    <album>Movie Classics</album>
    <album>Music From The Motion Picture Troy</album>
    <album>Once Around (Original Motion Picture Soundtrack)</album>
    <album>Pandora: The World of Avatar</album>
    <album>Seria Filmowa Empik - Fantastyka</album>
    <album>Soundtracks for Study</album>
    <album>Southpaw (Music From And Inspired By The Motion Picture)</album>
    <album>Southpaw (Original Motion Picture Soundtrack)</album>
    <album>Star Trek II- The Wrath of Khan (Original Motion Picture Soundtrack)</album>
    <album>Star Trek II- The Wrath of Khan Original Motion Picture Soundtrack</album>
    <album>Star Trek II: The Wrath of Khan (Original Motion Picture Soundtrack)</album>
    <album>Star Trek II: The Wrath of Khan Original Motion Picture Soundtrack</album>
    <album>Star Trek III- The Search For Spock (Original Motion Picture Soundtrack)</album>
    <album>Star Trek III: The Search For Spock (Original Motion Picture Soundtrack)</album>
    <album>The 33 (Original Motion Picture Soundtrack)</album>
    <album>The Alien Trilogy (Original Scores)</album>
    <album>The Amazing Spider-Man (Music from the Motion Picture)</album>
    <album>The Boy In The Striped Pyjamas</album>
    <album>The Classic Chillout Album</album>
    <album>The Giant of the Sea (Piano Themes Collection)</album>
    <album>The Journey of Natty Gann (Original Motion Picture Soundtrack)</album>
    <album>The Karate Kid (Music from the Motion Picture)</album>
    <album>The Lady in Red</album>
    <album>The Legend of Zorro</album>
    <album>The Life Before Her Eyes (Original Motion Picture Soundtrack)</album>
    <album>The Magnificent Seven (Original Motion Picture Soundtrack)</album>
    <album>The Mask of Zorro - Music from the Motion Picture</album>
    <album>The Missing</album>
    <album>The Name of the Rose (Original Soundtrack)</album>
    <album>The New World (Original Motion Picture Score)</album>
    <album>The Perfect Storm (Original Score)</album>
    <album>The Rocketeer (Original Motion Picture Soundtrack)</album>
    <album>The Spiderwick Chronicles (Original Motion Picture Score)</album>
    <album>The Spitfire Grill  - Original Soundtrack Recording</album>
    <album>Titanic (Original Motion Picture Soundtrack)</album>
    <album>Titanic 2-pack</album>
    <album>Titanic And Other Film Scores Of James Horner</album>
    <album>Titanic- Music from the Motion Picture Soundtrack</album>
    <album>Titanic- Original Motion Picture Soundtrack - Anniversary Edition</album>
    <album>Titanic- Original Motion Picture Soundtrack - Collector's Anniversary Edition</album>
    <album>Titanic- Special Edition</album>
    <album>Titanic: Music from the Motion Picture Soundtrack</album>
    <album>Titanic: Music from the Motion Picture Soundtrack - European Commercial Single</album>
    <album>Titanic: Original Motion Picture Soundtrack - Anniversary Edition</album>
    <album>Titanic: Original Motion Picture Soundtrack - Collector's Anniversary Edition</album>
    <album>Titanic: The Ultimate Collection</album>
    <album>We're Back! A Dinosaur's Story</album>
    <album>Where The River Runs Black (Original Motion Picture Soundtrack)</album>
    <album>Willow (Original Motion Picture Soundtrack)</album>
    <album>Wolf Totem (Jean-Jacques Annaud's Original Motion Picture Soundtrack)</album>
    <album>Wolf Totem (Original Soundtrack Album)</album>
    <album>WOLFEN Soundtrack</album>
  </albums>
</artist>