<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<artist>
  <name>Zbigniew Preisner</name>
  <albums>
    <album>10 Easy Pieces for Piano (Polish version, 10 Latwych Utworow Na Fortepian)</album>
    <album>A Woman in Berlin O.S.T</album>
    <album>A Woman in Berlin O.S.T.</album>
    <album>Aberdeen (Original Motion Picture Soundtrack)</album>
    <album>Aglaja (Original Motion Picture Soundtrack)</album>
    <album>Angelica (Original Motion Picture Soundtrack)</album>
    <album>At Play In The Fields Of The Lord</album>
    <album>Between Strangers (Original Motion Picture Soundtrack)</album>
    <album>Danse Macabre</album>
    <album>Dekalog (Original Film Soundtrack)</album>
    <album>Diaries of Hope</album>
    <album>Effroyables Jardins (Générique)</album>
    <album>Effroyables Jardins (Original Soundtrack)</album>
    <album>Europa Centrale (Original Motion Picture Soundtrack)</album>
    <album>Forgotten We'll Be (Original Motion Picture Soundtrack)</album>
    <album>Głosy</album>
    <album>Haunted Heart (Original Motion Picture Soundtrack)</album>
    <album>It's All About Love (Original Motion Picture Soundtrack)</album>
    <album>It's Not Too Late</album>
    <album>Kyrie Eleison - Byzantine Version (Original Motion Picture Soundtrack)</album>
    <album>La Double vie de Véronique (Original Film Soundtrack)</album>
    <album>La double vie de Véronique (Original Motion Picture Soundtrack) [Remastered]</album>
    <album>La Reina de España (Original Motion Picture Soundtrack)</album>
    <album>Lament (Radio Edit)</album>
    <album>Lost and Love (Original Motion Picture Soundtrack)</album>
    <album>Man of God (Original Motion Picture Soundtrack)</album>
    <album>Melancholy</album>
    <album>Mother Didn't Know (Original Motion Picture Soundtrack)</album>
    <album>Our World</album>
    <album>Preisner's Music (Best Of)</album>
    <album>Requiem for My Friend</album>
    <album>Silence, Night and Dreams</album>
    <album>The Beautiful Country</album>
    <album>The History of Eternity</album>
    <album>The Last September (Original Motion Picture Soundtrack)</album>
    <album>The Secret Garden (Original Motion Picture Soundtrack)</album>
    <album>Trois Couleurs- Bleu, Blanc, Rouge (Original Motion Picture Soundtrack from the Three Colors Trilogy by Kieślowski)</album>
    <album>Trois Couleurs: Bleu, Blanc, Rouge (Original Motion Picture Soundtrack from the Three Colors Trilogy by Kieślowski)</album>
    <album>Un Secret - Menachem & Fred (Original Motion Picture Soundtrack)</album>
    <album>Valley of Shadows (Original Motion Picture Soundtrack)</album>
    <album>W Poszukiwaniu Dróg. Nowe I Stare Kolędy</album>
    <album>Weiser (Original Motion Picture Soundtrack)</album>
    <album>Zbigniew Preisner i Przyjaciele Stare i Nowe Kolędy (Live Wroclaw 2020)</album>
  </albums>
</artist>