<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<artist>
  <name>Scooter</name>
  <albums>
    <album>...And The Beat Goes On!</album>
    <album>...And The Beat Goes On! (20 Years Of Hardcore Expanded Edition - Remastered)</album>
    <album>100% Scooter (25 Years Wild & Wicked)</album>
    <album>20 Years Of Hardcore (Remastered)</album>
    <album>24 Carat Gold</album>
    <album>Ace</album>
    <album>Age Of Love</album>
    <album>Age Of Love (20 Years Of Hardcore Expanded Edition - Remastered)</album>
    <album>Back To The Heavyweight Jam</album>
    <album>Back To The Heavyweight Jam (20 Years Of Hardcore Expanded Edition - Remastered)</album>
    <album>Encore - Live And Direct</album>
    <album>Excess All Areas - Live 2006</album>
    <album>God Save The Rave</album>
    <album>I Want You To Stream! (Live)</album>
    <album>Jumping All Over The World</album>
    <album>Jumping All over the World - Whatever You Want</album>
    <album>Jumping All Over The World (20 Years Of Hardcore Expanded Edition - Remastered 2013)</album>
    <album>Live - Selected Songs Of The 10th Anniversary Concert At Docks, Hamburg</album>
    <album>Mind The Gap</album>
    <album>Mind The Gap (20 Years Of Hardcore Expanded Edition - Remastered)</album>
    <album>Music For A Big Night Out</album>
    <album>No Time To Chill</album>
    <album>No Time To Chill (20 Years Of Hardcore Expanded Edition - Remastered)</album>
    <album>Open Your Mind And Your Trousers</album>
    <album>Our Happy Hardcore</album>
    <album>Our Happy Hardcore (20 Years Of Hardcore Expanded Edition - Remastered)</album>
    <album>Push The Beat For This Jam (The Second Chapter)</album>
    <album>Rough And Tough And Dangerous - The Singles 1994 - 1998</album>
    <album>Scooter - Live in Hamburg</album>
    <album>Scooter Forever</album>
    <album>Sheffield</album>
    <album>Sheffield (20 Years Of Hardcore Expanded Edition - Remastered)</album>
    <album>The Big Mash Up</album>
    <album>The Big Mash Up (20 Years Of Hardcore Expanded Edition - Remastered)</album>
    <album>The Big Mash Up (2012 Tour Edition)</album>
    <album>The Fifth Chapter</album>
    <album>The Stadium Techno Experience</album>
    <album>The Stadium Techno Experience (20 Years of Hardcore Expanded Editon)</album>
    <album>The Ultimate Aural Orgasm</album>
    <album>The Ultimate Aural Orgasm (20 Years Of Hardcore Expanded Edition - Remastered)</album>
    <album>Under The Radar Over The Top</album>
    <album>Under The Radar Over The Top (20 Years Of Hardcore Expanded Edition - Remastered)</album>
    <album>Under The Radar Over The Top (The Dark Side Editon)</album>
    <album>We Bring The Noise</album>
    <album>We Bring The Noise! (20 Years Of Hardcore Expanded Edition - Remastered)</album>
    <album>Who's Got The Last Laugh Now-</album>
    <album>Who's Got The Last Laugh Now- (20 Years Of Hardcore Expanded Edition - Remastered)</album>
    <album>Wicked!</album>
    <album>Wicked! (20 Years Of Hardcore Expanded Edition - Remastered)</album>
  </albums>
</artist>