<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<artist>
  <name>Jascha Heifetz</name>
  <albums>
    <album>Artists Of The Century: Jascha Heifetz</album>
    <album>Bach: Partitas & Concertos pour violon (Les indispensables de Diapason)</album>
    <album>Beethoven: Sonata No. 3 in E-Flat, Op. 12, No. 3, Sonata No. 6, Op. 30, No. 1 in A</album>
    <album>Beethoven: Violin Concerto - Mendelssohn: Violin Concerto</album>
    <album>Beethoven: Violin Concerto in D Major, Op. 61 - Mendelssohn: Violin Concerto in E Minor, Op. 64 (Heifetz Remastered)</album>
    <album>Brahms: Sonata No.3 in D Minor, Op.108, Wieniawski: Polonaise brillante No. 1, Op. 4, in D, Handel: Sonata, Op. 1, No. 13, in D</album>
    <album>Brahms: Violin Concerto in D</album>
    <album>Brahms: Violin Concerto in D Major, Op. 77 - Tchaikovsky: Violin Concerto in D Major, Op. 35 (Heifetz Remastered)</album>
    <album>Bruch: Violin Concerto No. 1</album>
    <album>Bruch: Violin Concerto No. 1 in G Minor, Op. 26 , Mozart: Violin Concerto No. 4, K.218, in D</album>
    <album>Glazunov: Violin Concerto in A Minor, Op. 82 , Mozart: Sinfonia concertante, K.364 in E-Flat</album>
    <album>Heifetz on Television</album>
    <album>Heifetz Violin Greatest Hits</album>
    <album>Heifetz: Encores</album>
    <album>Heifetz: Rediscovered</album>
    <album>Jascha Heifetz - It Ain't Necessarily So. Legendary classic and jazz studio takes</album>
    <album>Jascha Heifetz plays Beethoven (Sonatas & Concerto)</album>
    <album>Jascha Heifetz plays Sonatas for Violin</album>
    <album>Jascha Heifetz Violin Concertos - Original Album Classics</album>
    <album>Jean Sibelius: Concerto for Violin and Orchestra in D Minor, Op. 47 - En Saga, Op. 9 - Finlandia, Op. 26 (Recordings of 1935 - 1939)</album>
    <album>Johannes Brahms: Double Concerto for Violin and Cello in A minor, Op.102 - Antonín Dvořák: Piano Trio in F Minor, Op. 65</album>
    <album>Max Bruch: Violin Concerto No. 1 In G Minor, Op. 26 - Scottish Fantasy In E Flat Major, Op. 46</album>
    <album>Mendelson: String Octet, Op. 20, Jascha Heifetz vs. Alexandre Schneider (Compare 2 Versions)</album>
    <album>Mendelssohn-Bartholdy: Violin Concerto, Op. 64, in E Minor, Bruch: Scottish Fantasy</album>
    <album>Mendelssohn: Violin Concerto - Mozart: Violin Concertos Nos. 4 & 5 "Turkish"</album>
    <album>Sarasate: Zigeunerweisen, Op. 20, Saint-Saëns: Havanaise, Op. 83</album>
    <album>Sibelius: Violin Concerto in D Minor, Op. 47</album>
    <album>Sibelius: Violin Concerto in D Minor, Op. 47 - Prokofiev: Violin Concerto No. 2 in G Minor, Op. 63 - Glazunov: Violin Concerto in  (Heifetz Remastered)</album>
    <album>Tchaikovsky: Violin Concerto in D, Op. 35</album>
    <album>The Heifetz Collection</album>
    <album>The Heifetz Collection - Vol. 1 (1917 - 1924)</album>
    <album>The Heifetz Collection - Vol. 4</album>
    <album>The Magic of Jascha Heifetz (Remastered)</album>
    <album>The Very Best of Jascha Heifetz</album>
    <album>Vieuxtemps: Violin Concerto No. 5 in A Minor, Op. 37, Bruch: Scottish Fantasy, Op. 46</album>
    <album>Vitali: Chaconne in G Minor - Tedesco: The Lark - Fauré: Sonata No. 1, Op. 13, in A</album>
    <album>Walton: Violin Concerto - Castelnuovo-Tedesco: Violin Concerto No. 2, 'The Prophets'</album>
    <album>William Walton: Concerto for Violin in B Minor</album>
  </albums>
</artist>