<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<artist>
  <name>John Eliot Gardiner</name>
  <albums>
    <album>Berlioz : L'enfance du Christ</album>
    <album>Berlioz: Mélodies & Les nuits d'été</album>
    <album>Chabrier: L'étoile</album>
    <album>England, My England. The Story of Henry Purcell (Original Motion Picture Soundtrack)</album>
    <album>Gardiner conducts Berlioz, Bizet & Massenet, Messager</album>
    <album>Gardiner conducts Iphigénie en Aulide, La rencontre imprévue & Don Juan.</album>
    <album>Gluck : Iphigénie en Aulide</album>
    <album>Handel : Dixit Dominus & Zadok the Priest</album>
    <album>Handel : Water Music, Concerti grossi, Israel in Egypt, The Ways of Zion Do Mourn & Semele</album>
    <album>Handel Edition Volume 3 - L'Allegro, Il Penseroso ed il Moderato, Tamerlano, Alcina, Il Pastor Fido, Terpsichore</album>
    <album>Handel Edition Volume 5 - Semele, Israel in Egypt, Dixit Dominus, Zadok the Priest, La Resurrezione, The Ways of Zion do Mourn</album>
    <album>Handel Edition Volume 9 - Orchestral Music</album>
    <album>Handel: Dixit Dominus, HWV 232 & Coronation Anthem No. 1, HWV 258 "Zadok the Priest"</album>
    <album>John Eliot Gardiner - The Blossoming Conductor</album>
    <album>John Eliot Gardiner Conducts French Baroque Music: Couperin, Rameau, Campra & Leclair</album>
    <album>Leclair: Scylla et Glaucus, Op. 11</album>
    <album>Lehár: Die lustige Witwe</album>
    <album>Massenet: Scènes dramatiques, Scènes de féérie, Scènes alsaciennes & Scènes pittorresques</album>
    <album>Offenbach: Les brigands</album>
    <album>Purcell Edition Volume 3 : Odes, Anthems & Ceremonial Music</album>
    <album>Purcell Essentials</album>
    <album>Purcell: Edition Vol. 2. The Indian Queen, The Tempest, Dioclesian & Timon of Athens</album>
    <album>Purcell: King Arthur (Highlights)</album>
    <album>Purcell: King Arthur, Music for Queen Mary, Come Ye Sons of Art, Hail! Bright Cecilia, The Indian Queen, The Tempest…</album>
    <album>Purcell: King Arthur, Music for Queen Mary, Hail! Bright Cecilia, Timon of Athens, Dioclesian, The Indian Queen & The Tempest</album>
    <album>Purcell: King Arthur, Z. 628</album>
    <album>Purcell: Music for Queen Mary, Come ye Sons of Art</album>
    <album>Scarlatti: Stabat Mater - Clément: O Maria, vernans rosa - Gesualdo: Ave dulcissima Maria - Cavalli: Salve Regina</album>
    <album>Tchaikovsky: Rococo Variations, Andante cantabile, Pezzo capriccioso & Nocturne - Cello Works by Glazunov, Cui, Rimsky-Korsakov</album>
  </albums>
</artist>